[{"answer": "You know, I wish you wouldn't say harvest. We're talking about human beings, not brussel sprouts", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "So the locals aren't used to friendly visitors", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend! The mandates", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "And what if you are mistaken? I do not recognize this that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You say you don't remember me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Then do you remember this", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Excuse me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You know that's a really odd sound. I thought you just said you wouldn't go", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Did anyone else hear that kid say that that place'c was guilty already? For all we know, they wanna kill him", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Now see, it's that near as I can figure part that's got me a little worried. What if their idea of a simple trial is a simple beheading", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, you're outta luck, 'cause you're not gonna get him to pecca anything", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "That would be me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What does that mean", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How could there be such a person? Anyone who has a mind has an opinion", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend's father died by my hand. No one else's. I am responsible. What I did while serving Apophis, I will not hide from", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Then that is what I deserve", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "There were fifty human captives. All were unarmed. that place ordered me to slaughter them all", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I did not", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But you didn't, did you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What did you do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh, no where do you, where do you sleep at night? Where do you take shelter? Where do you sleep", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "The hiding", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So although you were faced with a terrible decision, you chose the lesser of two evils", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend, I'm told the my friend's only defense against the Goa'ulds is their ability to run and hide. Is that right", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "War criminals", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Cor-ai.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "General my friend, I have spent a lot of years in the service of my country, and I have been ordered to do some damned distasteful things. I will not allow them to execute my friend", "qsentId": 26}]